- You have never done that before.
- Yes.
- Have you?
- At Tanja.
But...
It's a pretend grandmother, so that's another thing.
This is a friend-friend.
Buddy buddy.
Along the way, we should actually stop and look for some new clothes, because we have to supplement before school starts.
You don't like jeans, so you need a little more type of tight stuff I think, huh?
- Yes.
- A little cool things.
Harry likes jeans, but he needs a little more soft pants and stuff.
- Yes, he has a lot of jeans.
- Yes.
We will see what we find so that you are good looking and nice, because if less than two weeks start ...
- To me and to Harry.
- Yes, to you two.
And sleeping bag for dad.
Old, from the seventies, but works great.
And last but not least...
Supermodern sleeping bag for mom.
My superhero costumes are not in here.
- What an osis.
- Yes.
Can we go to the school yard for a little while?
Yes we can do that.
And then we can test our new clothes and take some pictures for Instagram.
- Yay!
Yay!
- Check out what nicely, we match.
- Look!
Come then, try to take it!
Alma and Harry.
A completely natural situation.
So here we always lie.
Don't all families do it?
- The kids feel relaxed ... - But hello, stop with that!
- Wow, the worst thumbnail.
- Yes, I say so!
Do you feel ready for autumn and school and preschool?
No.
So, I say no because I have thought that the summer holidays have been too short.
Do you feel ready for the fall?
Comment below.
Below...
Now I'm going to swing a little.
Harry wants to swing himself, he says.
I can't swing him.